Hello friends, regarding Step Towards Investment
YouTube2, its stock closed today at
26000.375 with a gain of 3.18.
So let's talk
about its date.
Abbott India Limited announced its quarter
four results yesterday along with a
final dividend of 410. Yes
friends, 410. Yes, 410.
And for this, Abbott India Limited has
kept a record date of July 19, 2024.
Now let's talk about Bharat Petroleum
Corporation Limited. Its
stock closed today at
618.8 with a gain of 4.50. That is, with a gain of 45.
So let's talk
about its update. This company has
disclosed its quarter four results yesterday
and along with that, this company has
also announced a bonus issue
in the ratio of two, that is, if you have
one share of this company, then it will become two shares,
if you have two, then it will become four, that is,
you have  All the shares of this company will
double and the
record date for this payment
is June 22,
2024. Along with this, this company has
also announced a final dividend of ₹1. This translates
into a final dividend of
₹
10.5 per share post the bonus issue.
This company has
not announced any record date for this final dividend,
but as soon as this company announces the
record date or ex-
date for this final dividend, I will tell you
about Information Company Limited, its shares
closed at 16635 with a rise of 75 points today. So let's talk
about its update. Today, a
block deal was seen in ICICI Lord Insurance Company
and this block deal was done
at 172.5. In this block deal, Bharatiya
Enterprises
sold 8.5 lakh shares at ₹1722 per share and
IIC Bank bought 21 lakh shares and
Axis Mutual Fund bought 4 lakh shares.  Shares have been purchased;
Morgan Stanley Asia Singapore Pvt has
bought 4.5 lakh shares; Goldman Sachs
Singapore Pvt has
bought 2.25 lakh shares; Blackstone
Q Master Sub Fund has
bought 75 lakh shares; and others. Now let's
talk about Indian Renewable Energy
Development Agency Limited (IREDA),
i.e., Dai. Its stock
closed at 16,550 today with a gain of 42 per cent. So let's talk
about its update. Dai has set
up a subsidiary in GIFT City to mobilize
global funds for green projects. So
let's understand this update in a little detail.
Indian Renewable Energy Development
Agency Limited (IREDA) has incorporated
a wholly owned subsidiary in the International
Financial Services Centre located in
Gujarat's GIFT City to extend its
global reach for securing funds at
competitive
rates to boost green projects in the
country. The Ministry of Renewable Energy
said on Thursday. Now let's talk
about Adani Enterprises Limited (ADANI). Its
stock has  Today it has
given a closing at 2803.90 with a rise of 1.35, so let's talk
about its update. Adani
Enterprises Limited's Mauritius base
arm
Adani Global
acquired 49 stake in UAE base Sirius Digitech for 24500. Now let's talk
about Rail Vikas Nigam Limited
i.e. RVNL, its
share has given a closing at 261.60 with a rise of 21 today,
so let's talk
about its update. RVNL has
got an order of Rs 38 crore 1024 818 67 from South East Central Railway and this order has to be
completed by RV NL in 15 months i.e.
in 1 year 3 months. So friends, if you like
this video information